{
    "subject": "resource/Thunderbird_Films",
    "predicate": "property/locationCity",
    "object": "resource/British_Columbia",
    "human_readable": "The location city of Thunderbird Films is British Columbia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.85918128490448,
            "question": "Where is Thunderbird Films located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6990404725074768,
            "question": "Is Thunderbird Films based in a city or a region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6931467652320862,
            "question": "In which Canadian region is Thunderbird Films situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5012985467910767,
            "question": "What province is the home of Thunderbird Films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31512516736984253,
            "question": "Could Thunderbird Films be involved in the film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2620967924594879,
            "question": "What is the largest city in British Columbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22876496613025665,
            "question": "Are there any other notable businesses located in British Columbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2187522053718567,
            "question": "What type of business is Thunderbird Films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20411574840545654,
            "question": "Does Thunderbird Films have a website or social media presence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11228378117084503,
            "question": "What natural features are characteristic of British Columbia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location city of Thunderbird Films is British Columbia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_317_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Thunderbird Films have a website or social media presence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_317_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of business is Thunderbird Films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_317_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable businesses located in British Columbia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_317_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_317_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_317_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_317_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_317_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_317_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_317_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_317_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_317_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_317_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_317_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that according to the context information, the triple \"The location city of Thunderbird Films is British Columbia\" is supported by the documents. The text states that \"Thunderbird Films collaborates with talented producers, maximizing the financial and creative benefits of Canadian co-production...\" and later mentions \"Vancouver, BC based entertainment production and distribution company Thunderbird Films\". This implies that Thunderbird Films has a connection to Vancouver, which is located in British Columbia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: Based on the information provided, particularly from `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_317/re-ranker-msmarco/32.txt`, Thunderbird Films is described as a \"Vancouver-based entertainment production and distribution company,\" which indicates that its location city is British Columbia, Canada."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}